sanriotown.com 2010-06-10

# Sanriotown - Privacy Policy

**OVERVIEW**

We, Sanriotown.com, respect you, our user, and your privacy. It is our policy to comply with internationally recognized standards of personal data privacy protection and, in Hong Kong, with the Personal Data (Privacy)Ordinance (the "Ordinance"). For further information about the Ordinance, please visit [http://www.pco.org.hk/ord](http://www.pco.org.hk/).) 

This statement set outs our privacy policies and practices in relation to the following: 

  1. What information is collected 
  2. How the information is used 
  3. With whom the information is shared 
  4. How we protect children under the age of 13 
  5. How you access or change your personally identifiable information 

**WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**

We collect three kinds of information from you. 

The first kind is personally identifiable information ("Personally Identifiable Information") which we collect during your registration for any sanriotown.com services such as E-mail, chat, message board, web hosting¡K etc ("Services"). Personally Identifiable Information includes your first and last name, year of birth, gender, country, occupation, annual income range, education, household size and alternative contact address. 

The second kind is non-personally identifiable information which includes your IP address (your computer's unique signature), operating system, browser software, Internet Service Provider, domain type and other numeric codes which identify a computer ("Aggregated Information"). 

We use cookies to collect the Aggregated Information without your being aware of this. A cookie is a very small text file placed on your hard drive by a web server with your permission for record-keeping purposes. Once you register on one of our web sites, cookies will be used to make a record of the pages you visit and your passwords and preferences. Since cookies cannot contain any program codes, they cannot be used to carry viruses nor can they be used to extract data from your computer. Only the server that sets cookies can access the information saved by using cookies. 

Since the functioning of our system depends on our use of cookies, our web sites do not allow access by users who do not accept cookies. 

The third kind is personal information which we collect during your subscription for certain email marketing programs such as opt-in email, opt-in newsletter, polling and special promotions ("Subscription Information"). Subscription Information includes all your Personally Identifiable Information, your email address and topic(s) interested to you. 

**HOW INFORMATION IS USED**

Personally Identifiable Information is used solely for the purpose of identifying, managing and servicing individual user. 

Aggregated Information is collected to help us to compile aggregate statistics on site usage and to analyse our users' demographics, interests and behaviour. This will give us a better understanding of the needs of our users and design our services and products accordingly. 

Subscription Information is used to deliver the emails or newsletters to users who have chosen to subscribe to such emails or newsletters. 

**WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION IS SHARED**

We do not disclose any of your Personally Identifiable Information to any third parties except: 

  * with your written permission; or 
  * as required by any applicable law; or 
  * to our Enterprise Partners and Co-brand Partners as explained below. 

We only share your Personally Identifiable Information with sanriotown.com's partners in accordance with our operating agreements with them. We recommend that you review the privacy policy statements of our partner at its home page (http://www.outblaze.com) for further details. 

We only share the Aggregate Information about our users with our advertising partners. We need to do this so that our advertising partners can target their advertisements at the right audiences. Please however note that we do not give your Personally Identifiable Information to any of our advertising partners. You may request us to send to you further details of any advertisements on our web sites. We will ask our relevant advertising partners for those details and forward them to you by e-mail. For such request, please contact info@sanriotown.com. 

We only share the Subscription Information with email marketers that sanriotown.com carefully selected to work with us in order to provide users emails or newsletter they selected to receive. We need to disclose the Subscription Information to the email marketers in order for users to receive the correct emails or newsletters which they opt-in to receive. The opt-in procedure is another method to ensure that users will only receive materials they wanted to receive. Any of our e-mails to you containing marketing materials will also include the details of an opt-out procedure under which you may choose not to receive any further marketing e-mails. If you have any questions regarding marketing e-mails from us or any third parties, please contact info@sanriotown.com. 

Please be aware that when you click on the advertising banners on our web sites or in any marketing emails, you may be linked to sites which are not operated by us. We are not responsible for the collection or use of any information which you provide to those sites. We strongly recommend that you should review the privacy policy statements of those sites which collect information from you. 

**HOW WE PROTECT CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13**

Sanriotown.com does not collect personal information from persons under the age of 13. In order to ensure adherence to this policy, the opening page of our website asks for the date, month and year of birth of each visitor and denies further access to visitors whose birth date shows that they are under 13 years of age. If you believe that a child under 13 has gained access to the sanriotown.com site, or if you have any questions concerning sanriotown.com’s privacy policy and practices, please contact us at: 

**Sanrio Digital (HK) Ltd**  
Unit 418-421, Level 4, Cyberport 1,  
100 Cyberport Road  
Hong Kong  
Email: [info@sanriotown.com](mailto:info@sanriotow.com)

**HOW YOU ACCESS OR CHANGE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
You have the right to access and change any of your Personally Identifiable Information collected by us. If you would like to access or change your information, please follow the simple instruction in your user account option or please contact us at [info@sanriotown.com](mailto:info@sanriotown.com). 

**GENERAL**  
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy Statement at any time without prior notice and only the current Privacy Policy Statement may be deemed effective. 

By registering for any of our services, you also consent to the transfer of any of your information collected by us to a jurisdiction outside Hong Kong which may not have any laws protecting personal data similar to the Ordinance. 

If you have any questions concerning our use of your personal information, please contact us at: 

**Sanrio Digital (HK) Ltd**  
Unit 418-421, Level 4, Cyberport 1,  
100 Cyberport Road  
Hong Kong  
Email: [info@sanriotown.com](mailto:info@sanriotow.com)

Last updated September/2006
